hi spring fans in today's installment of
嗨，今天的系列中的春季粉丝
spring tips we're gonna go ahead and
春天的提示，我们要继续前进，
take a look at different ways to observe
看一下观察的不同方式
the sort of state of the system in
系统中的状态
previous installments we've looked at
我们看过的前几期
for example Cloud Foundry and we looked
例如Cloud Foundry，我们看了看
at how you can get a sort of at a glance
一目了然
perspective of the state of the system
系统状态的观点
based on the way the platform sees
根据平台的观察方式
things and we looked at spring cloud
事情，我们看着春天的云
dataflow which also gives you a very
数据流也给您非常
convenient sort of up centric
方便的向上中心
perspective on messaging based
基于消息传递的观点
micro-services but there are some also
微服务，但也有一些
some nice alternative approaches to
一些不错的替代方法
visualizing or understanding the sort of
可视化或理解某种
layout of your system the structure of
系统布局的结构
your system and both of these things
您的系统以及这两件事
that we're gonna look at today or
我们今天要看的是
Dinah's J works
黛娜的J作品
micro-services dashboard and the spring
微服务仪表板和春天
boot admin both work very well in
引导管理员都可以很好地工作
conjunction with Spring clouds discovery
与Spring Cloud Discovery结合
client abstractions so any service
客户抽象，因此任何服务
registry that you use through the
您通过
service read through the discovery
通过发现读取服务
client abstraction will work just fine
客户端抽象将很好地工作
and it can be used to discover the
它可以用来发现
relevant nodes in the system so this
系统中的相关节点，因此
makes it a sort of you know no cost win
令您有点不知所措
right you can just add a dashboard one
正确，您只需添加一个仪表板
of these two dashboards I'm gonna look
我要看的这两个仪表板
at today to get sort of a map or a sort
在今天得到某种地图或某种
of bird's eye view of the whole system
整个系统的鸟瞰图
at a glance which is enviable when
令人羡慕的一瞥
you're trying to build a system that has
您正在尝试建立一个具有
a lot of notes a lot of moving parts
很多音符很多活动部件
okay so we're gonna we need to set up a
好吧，我们要设置一个
few prerequisites here first we're gonna
首先要满足一些先决条件
set up a eureka service registry so
设置一个尤里卡服务注册表，这样
we'll build that here and we'll
我们将在这里建立它，我们将
configure this because we need to sort
配置这个，因为我们需要排序
we need a service ready and I mention or
我们需要准备好服务，我提到或
you can use any service registry that
您可以使用任何服务注册表
you want and that's true of course but
你想要的，那当然是对的，但是
we you know Eureka is very simple to
我们知道尤里卡很简单
setup you could also use alternatively
设置您也可以使用
hash eco console you could use Apache
您可以使用Apache的哈希生态控制台
zookeeper you could use a conf under
zookeeper，您可以在下面使用conf
itself I mean anything that has a for
本身，我的意思是说任何具有
which there's a discovery client
有一个发现客户端
abstraction will work just fine so let's
抽象将正常工作，所以让我们
spin this up we'll go to our Java class
旋转它，我们将去我们的Java课
here and we'll say at enable you week
在这里，我们会告诉您启用周
Gus server okay and we'll go to
Gus服务器正常，我们将转到
application up properties spring cloud
应用性能春云
so spring that application dot name
所以春天那个应用程序点名称
equals
等于
week - service and we'll spin this up
周-服务，我们将逐步解决
import 87-61
进口87-61
and that'll do that's this that's the
那会做到的就是
registry now we need a few clients we
注册现在我们需要一些客户
need a few things to visualize otherwise
需要一些东西来可视化
this wouldn't be much of a dashboard if
如果这不是仪表板的话
we had another thing to sort of discover
我们还有另一件事要发现
and work with so let's go build our
并与之合作，让我们开始建立我们的
first client will call this one client a
第一位客户将这个客户称为
and what we're gonna do is we going to
而我们要做的是
add the web support and actuator that's
添加网络支持和执行器
important we need actuator for some of
重要的是我们需要一些执行器
this right that gives us some some very
这项权利给了我们一些
useful information so we'll have now the
有用的信息，所以我们现在有了
discovery client you know you Iike
发现客户，您认识您Iike
service registry just the discovery
服务注册表只是发现
client implementation why add that to
客户实施为什么要添加到
the classpath we'll call that client a
我们称该客户为
and we'll generate another one called
我们将生成另一个名为
client be very imaginative and these are
客户很有想象力，这些是
just rest api is i mean you know these
休息api是我的意思是你知道这些
are just your average hypothetical
只是您的平均假设
micro-service api is right so here we go
微服务api是正确的，所以我们开始
client a client B and we have here we
客户客户B，我们在这里
can see in the console that Eureka is
可以在控制台中看到Eureka是
trying to register itself with itself so
试图向自己注册
localhost 87-61 Oh
本地87-61哦
serve it up port that's why it's trying
为港口服务，这就是为什么要尝试
to register itself with itself and it
向自己和自己注册
can't find itself because it's not
找不到自己，因为它不是
running on the standard port that it's
在它的标准端口上运行
usually and now of course that's a
通常，现在当然是
property that you could specify to point
您可以指定指向的属性
it to a different instance or even
它到另一个实例甚至
better there's a property you can you
最好有一个你可以的财产
could specify it to to say don't
可以指定它说不
register yourself but for our purposes
注册自己，但出于我们的目的
just it's fine to just rectify it
只是纠正一下就可以了
because we don't I don't want to get too
因为我们不，我也不想得到
much into the weeds on setting up a you
建立您的杂草
week of industry
工业周
good working now we're cooking and
现在工作顺利，我们正在做饭，
[Music]
[音乐]
that'll do that'll be a that'll be our
那会做那将是我们的
instance now let's go back to client a
现在让我们回到客户端
here and we need to say that this is
在这里，我们需要说的是
called client a and in our code we'll
称为客户a，在我们的代码中
just build a very simple endpoint here
只是在这里建立一个非常简单的端点
did I type that in twice you know that's
我有两次输入吗，你知道那是
fine plenty application we're gonna
很好的应用程序，我们要
activate the service registration
激活服务注册
discovery support so I'm able discovery
发现支持，因此我能够发现
client that's the same meditation
冥想相同的客户
regardless of the implementation and
不管实施和
we're gonna make this rest controller
我们要让这个休息控制器
just a simple rest controller and we're
只是一个简单的休息控制器，我们
gonna call this one name or turn a and
会叫这个名字或变成a和
get mapping okay so now in until he goes
可以绘制地图了，所以直到他走了
to four slash they'll get the name of
到四个斜杠，他们将得到
the service we could also just go to the
我们也可以去的服务
info endpoint and configure spring that
信息端点并配置spring
application that ID if we wanted to to
如果需要，请使用该ID
show up there but this is fine okay so
出现在这里，但这很好，所以
this is very simple service we're just
这是非常简单的服务，我们只是
gonna spin it up right we don't I'm not
要把它旋转起来，我们不是，我不是
here to talk about configuring our
在这里谈论配置我们的
writing micro services we're gonna talk
编写我们要谈论的微服务
about observing them marching them so
观察他们的游行
this is our first service here we're
这是我们在这里的第一项服务
gonna copy that
要复制那个
save ourselves a precious piece teach
为自己保存一份宝贵的知识
keystrokes and and then rinse repeat
击键，然后重复冲洗
here with client be client be client
在这里与客户成为客户
okay
好的
client be application and we're done
客户申请，我们就完成了
okay there's this so now we've got
好的，有这个，所以现在我们有了
client be up and running well we name
客户端运行良好，我们命名
this to be B and we'll change this to be
这是B，我们将其更改为
on another port of course so spring that
当然是在另一个港口
application that name equals client B
名称等于客户端B的应用程序
server dot port equals eighty eighty one
服务器点端口等于88
because the other one will have spun up
因为另一个会旋转
on port 8080 by default we need to
默认情况下，在端口8080上，我们需要
preclude collisions there
避免在那里发生碰撞
and now we have a few things we can do
现在我们有几件事可以做
here we have a few types of dashboards
这里我们有几种类型的仪表板
that we can look at right so we've got
我们可以看正确的，所以我们有
client a there's that client B should
客户A，客户B应该
joining us here at any second now
现在随时加入我们
I hope there it is so there's client B
我希望那里是客户B
there both on you know this is on a
你们两个都知道这在一个
standard port port 8080 so it's fine
标准端口8080，所以很好
this is on port 8081 they're both
这是在8081端口上
available they both have actuators so if
可用，它们都有执行器，所以如果
we go to the info endpoint we go to the
我们转到信息端点，然后转到
the metrics endpoint for example let's
指标端点，例如
install my browser plug-in here
在这里安装我的浏览器插件
extensions and JSON view seems to be
扩展和JSON视图似乎是
constantly disabling itself extension
不断禁用自身扩展
contains a serious security
包含严重的安全性
vulnerability I will have to look into
我将不得不研究的漏洞
that later but for now we need this so
那以后但是现在我们需要这个
here we are
我们来了
there's our endpoint there's the
这是我们的终点
endpoint with information right and this
具有信息权的端点
is the actual the actual are just
是实际的，实际的只是
surfaces information about each
表面有关每个的信息
individual node things that you can use
您可以使用的单个节点的东西
to observe what's happening right this
观察正在发生的事情
is very much inspired by for example
受到很多启发
what Google does they have the Google
Google有什么Google
Borg amnon approach right the Borgman
博格·阿姆农（Borg Amnon）接近博格曼
Borg monitoring approach and the Borg
博格监测方法和博格
monitoring approach steeply it said
监测方法陡然说
every service you know should articulate
您知道的每项服务都应明确表述
its own state it should be observable it
它自己的状态应该是可观察的
should provide information that
应提供以下信息
operators and and others can use to
操作员和其他人可以用来
understand the state of the application
了解应用程序的状态
and who better to articulate that state
谁能更好地表达那种状态
than the service itself so these are
比服务本身，所以这些是
endpoints well-known endpoints that
终结点
provide well known payloads that are
提供众所周知的有效载荷
germane to the state of this particular
与该特定状态有关
service and and this is useful if you
服务，这对您很有用
know where to look you can find this
知道在哪里可以找到这个
information on every single service it's
有关每个服务的信息
it's not generated by an adjacent
它不是由相邻的生成的
process it's not a Java monitoring agent
处理它不是Java监视代理
that sits underneath the process it's
位于流程的下方
not a sound of it's not another process
没有声音，这不是另一个过程
in the same container and the same node
在同一容器和同一节点中
instead it's in the Java code itself
相反，它在Java代码本身中
right and so you can customize this
对的，所以您可以自定义此
using code right you can change and
使用正确的代码，您可以更改和
articulate particular information if you
阐明特定信息，如果您
want and the defaults are also very
想要和默认值也非常
useful so metrics is one endpoint health
有用，因此指标是一个端点健康
certainly is a is another right so
当然是另一种权利，所以
here's health there's health and
这里的健康那里的健康和
I think Oh - 881 I got the same
我想哦-881我也一样
information right I get the same kind of
信息权我得到的是同一种
perspective there's as endpoints I think
观点，我认为有一个终点
endpoints actuator there's mappings we
端点执行器我们有映射
can always use mappings mappings tells
始终可以使用映射映射告诉
us what endpoints are available and I
我们哪些端点可用，我
guess this is looking for the endpoint
猜猜这是在寻找端点
that tells me what endpoints are
告诉我什么是端点
auto-config health heap dump config
自动配置运行状况堆转储配置
props are chaos in V resume methods
V恢复方法中道具混乱
maybe I was just thinking of this I
也许我只是在想这个
didn't write this is here so you can get
没有写这是在这里，所以你可以得到
all sorts of cool information from this
各种各样的酷信息
endpoint if you want this information is
端点，如果您希望此信息是
that all in JSON that's a rest service
JSON中的所有内容都是REST服务
there's a way you can get this
有办法可以得到这个
information via JMX as well right so but
也可以通过JMX获得信息
the problem is you have to know where to
问题是你必须知道在哪里
find the service you have to know where
找到您必须知道的服务
this information is and then you have to
该信息是，然后您必须
be able to read it and parse it and
能够阅读并解析它，并且
visualize it and so on and that gets
可视化它等等
tedious so one way to sort of understand
乏味，所以一种理解的方式
this information and kind of aggregate
这些信息和种类
it and make it easier to consume it is
它并使其更易于食用
to use the the spring boot admin from
从使用spring boot admin
from code centric so let's take a look
以代码为中心，让我们看一下
at that first okay so so what we're
首先，所以我们
gonna do is we're gonna go to start the
我们要做的是开始
spring an IO and we're going to build a
创建一个IO，我们将建立一个
spring boot to admin instance from a
spring boot 从管理实例
vanilla spring good application so we'll
香草弹簧良好的应用程序，所以我们会
bring in a web support or bring in
引入网络支持或引入
Eureka Service registration discovery
尤里卡服务注册发现
support actuator support I'm going to
支持执行器支持
hit generate now this will be our
点击生成现在这将是我们的
instance okay and what we're gonna do is
实例还可以，我们要做的是
we're gonna open this up and tell it to
我们要打开它并告诉
become an admin server but we need to to
成为管理服务器，但我们需要
add the code centric Springwood admin
添加以代码为中心的Springwood管理员
dependencies to to make this a admin
使其成为管理员的依赖项
server so right now the current
服务器现在是当前
incarnation is version 1.4 dot 4 so
化身是版本1.4点4
we'll use that there's two bits there's
我们将使用两个位
the user interface itself and then the
用户界面本身，然后
the backend API and after these could be
后端API，之后可能是
co-located in the same note as we're
与我们位于同一音符中
doing here or you could separate them so
在这里做，否则您可以将它们分开
we have to bring in both
我们必须同时引入
that said this is a natural thing to
说这是很自然的事情
extract out into a property so consider
提取到一个属性，所以考虑
doing that okay we place it all in this
这样做好了，我们将其全部放入
file thank you now there's a few ways
文件谢谢你现在有几种方法
for the Springwood admin to discover
让Springwood管理员发现
other knows as I mentioned the the
正如我提到的，其他人知道
easiest way for us is just use the
对我们来说最简单的方法就是使用
spring cloud discovery pine abstraction
春季云发现松树抽象
so we say at enable admin server up to
所以我们说在启用管理服务器
the Springwood admin and then we say at
Springwood管理员，然后我们在
enable discovery pride there is
使发现自豪
optionally a second alternative you know
您可以选择第二种选择
a second idea which is to use the
第二个想法是使用
Springwood admin client and I don't know
Springwood管理员客户端，我不知道
I think I'd stay away from a an extra
我想我会远离额外的
dependency on that on the client side
对客户端的依赖
I'd prefer if I could just make this all
我希望我能做到所有这些
work you know soup to nuts without
工作，你知道汤到坚果没有
having to add any extra dependencies
必须添加任何额外的依赖项
besides service registration and
除了服务注册和
discovery to my services now that said
现在发现我的服务说
spring that application dot name equals
春天，应用程序点名称等于
spring but-- admin we're going to run
春天，但是-管理员，我们要运行
this on port 8080 too and that should do
在端口8080上也应该这样做
it that should be everything we need to
那应该是我们需要的一切
to run the application let's go ahead
运行该应用程序，让我们继续
and spin it up and this is going to spin
并旋转它，这将旋转
up in a little talk to the other
和对方聊一聊
services as they've been registered in
已注册的服务
the registry and it'll show us
注册表，它会告诉我们
information that it's going to go on by
将会持续的信息
mining the information from the actual
从实际中挖掘信息
end points right so here's this yes I
终点正确，所以这是我
would like the allow notifications there
想要那里的允许通知
we go it's very cool huh
我们去很酷吧
so this is it's it's showing us the
这就是它向我们展示了
service registry itself it's showing us
服务注册表本身正在向我们展示
client a and B and we can click on these
客户a和B，我们可以点击这些
details the drop down first of all and
首先详细说明下拉列表，然后
we can see that these in points
我们可以看到这些
correspond to the to the end points in
对应于中的端点
the actuators right these are the very
这些执行器就非常
information the very the the menu of
信息非常的菜单
options that I was trying to find when I
我尝试寻找的选项
was looking in the actuator JSON output
在寻找执行器的JSON输出
is now clean Li and plainly presented to
现在是干净的李，并明确地向
me right here you can also see that this
我在这里你也可以看到
application has these very handy browser
应用程序具有这些非常方便的浏览器
notifications right that's a very nice
正确的通知，这非常好
feature so as things happen is the
功能，以便事情发生时
heartbeat events get emitted from these
这些发出心跳事件
different nodes and they come into they
不同的节点，它们进入它们
big they get registered into the EM into
大他们被注册到EM
the registry we can see that
注册表我们可以看到
automatically online here in Leah and in
在利亚和这里自动在线
the monitor and the dashboard so now we
显示器和仪表板，所以现在我们
can see that the Springwood admin has
可以看到Springwood管理员拥有
been read
被阅读
and it's available now if I click on any
如果我单击任何它，现在可以使用
one of these let's say they we click on
其中之一，假设我们点击
client B right go to metrics we can see
客户B正确选择我们可以看到的指标
there's a very convenient little
有一个非常方便的小
dashboard here with all the sort of
各种仪表板
metrics that we saw reflected on the
我们看到的指标反映在
forward slash metrics endpoint in the
中的正斜杠指标端点
application itself but they're all
应用程序本身，但它们都是
visualized right so this is very very
可视化的权利，所以这是非常非常
useful because you know we can add a
有用，因为您知道我们可以添加一个
glance to kind of understand what these
一眼就知道这些是什么
numbers mean what they should mean right
数字意味着他们应该说的对
if we can see the numbers are drawn for
如果我们看到数字是为
us to you know visualize for us this is
我们知道，为我们想象这是
not just the metrics right the the
不只是指标正确
environment itself the environment
环境本身环境
endpoint the env endpoint shows us a
端点端点向我们显示了一个
enumeration of the system properties and
系统属性的枚举和
the environment variables in that local
该局部环境变量
node we can see all that reflected
节点，我们可以看到所有反映出来的
specifically in the environment and it's
特别是在环境中
actually separated out by different
实际上被不同
property sources it looks like so here's
属性来源看起来像这样
the the enviros system environment
环境系统环境
versus the you know java properties JVM
与您知道的Java属性JVM
properties etc so all this stuff is all
属性等，所有这些东西就全部
separated out here and it's easy to read
分开在这里，很容易阅读
and easy to visualize and of course you
并易于可视化，当然您
can see which profiles are active which
可以看到哪些配置文件处于活动状态
is very convenient so maybe you have
非常方便，所以也许你有
certain properties are available only
某些属性仅可用
for a certain profile again all this
对于某个特定的配置文件
information you can get by explicitly
您可以明确获得的信息
looking at the the endpoint itself but
看端点本身，但是
why right yet so it's all readily
为什么还对，所以一切都很容易
interrogated and worked with here
被审问并在这里工作
there's another thing that's really nice
还有另一件事真的很好
is you can change properties for that
你可以改变它的属性吗
particular node you know here there's a
您知道这里有一个特定的节点
that's just that's something you can do
那就是你可以做的
in the in the application itself of
在应用程序本身中
course using the the the endpoints the
当然使用端点
actuator points using post and so on but
使用杆等执行器点，但
but it's nice to be able to do that all
但是能够做到这一切真是太好了
visually and interactively from this
从视觉上和交互上
sort of operator friendly console and of
操作员友好型控制台和
course it's nice to be able to filter
当然可以过滤
down as I've just done here the the
就像我刚刚在这里所做的那样
number of possible or applicable
可能或适用的数量
properties so I think that's very
属性，所以我认为这非常
convenient naturally we could view the
方便自然我们可以查看
JSON just like we did before right so
就像我们之前所做的那样，JSON
here's the env endpoint
这是环境端点
this is what we would have gotten if we
这就是我们得到的
had gone to the endpoint ourselves oh no
我们自己去了终点哦，不
this isn't this is actually the JSON
这不是，实际上是JSON
that the admin has has taken from that
管理员从中获取的
node right so that's
节点正确，所以
convenient as well the logging
方便记录
information
信息
this isn't configured I don't have this
这个没有配置，我没有这个
configured but it shows you how to do
配置，但它告诉您如何做
that it shows you configure Jolokia and
它显示您配置Jolokia和
then how to configure log back if you
那么如何配置回日志，如果您
want to and then you can actually set
想要，然后您可以实际设置
and specify and you know override
并指定，您知道覆盖
logging levels right from this very
从这个角度开始记录级别
convenient dashboard there's also if you
方便的仪表板
have Jolokia you can also access this
有Jolokia，您也可以访问此
information from JMX right so that would
来自JMX的信息，这样
be very convenient and threads so if you
非常方便和线程化，因此，如果您
want to see what's running which winds
想看看正在运行什么风
are kind of blocked or idle this is all
是被阻止还是闲置，仅此而已
sort of at a glance understandable and
一眼就可以理解，
visualizable you can click on any one of
可视化，您可以单击以下任意一项
them you can see the sort of deep thread
他们你可以看到那种深层次的线索
dump and so on and so on and we have
转储等等等等，我们有
trace now trace is a trace is actually
跟踪现在跟踪是一个跟踪实际上
just the request log write trace is not
只是请求日志写跟踪不是
distribute tracing it's a request log
分发跟踪它是一个请求日志
and it shows you which requests have
它告诉你哪些请求有
been made what endpoints the the
取得了哪些端点
responses and the headers and all that
响应，标题和所有其他内容
stuff so this is actually a a very very
东西，所以这实际上是一个非常非常
convenient visualization it shows you
方便的可视化显示
when chronologically it shows you this
按时间顺序向您显示
very convenient visualization of when
非常方便的可视化时间
requests happened this court this
请求发生在这个法院
corresponds of course to the the trace
当然对应于轨迹
endpoint itself and the trace endpoint
端点本身和跟踪端点
itself by default keep the last 100
本身默认保持最后100
requests in memory so you can customize
内存中的请求，因此您可以自定义
all that if you like and of course
当然，如果您愿意的话
there's heap dump which will download
有堆转储将下载
the same thing that we downloaded
我们下载的相同的东西
earlier so we have all this very very
较早，所以我们非常非常
cool information all at a glance right
一目了然的酷信息
we also have the this sort of general
我们也有这样的一般
view shows you the health right you're
视图显示您的健康状况
gonna care about that if any of these
会在意这些
are read you've got a problem right
读到你有问题吧
everything seems to be happy now and
现在一切似乎都很幸福，
I'll show you the memory it'll show you
我会告诉你的记忆会告诉你
the JVM it'll show you the arbiter
JVM，它将向您显示仲裁者
collection I mean just do it sort of a
收集我的意思是只是做一个
glance really important stuff that
看一眼真正重要的东西
you're gonna care about right so I like
你会关心正确的，所以我喜欢
I like the spring boot admin I think
我喜欢我认为的Spring Boot管理员
it's very very convenient for sort of
这非常方便
easily working with and navigating
轻松使用和导航
through all your different applications
通过您所有不同的应用程序
but it doesn't really give us a map does
但这并没有真正给我们一张地图
it it makes it easy to do at a glance
一目了然
interrogate or understand what the
询问或了解
surfaces are doing but it doesn't show
表面在做，但没有显示
you how they relate to each other so for
您如何彼此联系，以便
that we're gonna look at the or Dena Jay
我们要看的是Dena Jay或
works micro services dashboard now what
现在可以使用微服务仪表板
we're going to do is we're going to
我们要做的是
build a
建个
micro-services dashboard same in the
微服务仪表板在
very same way as we did the spring good
就像我们把春天做好一样
admin we're just gonna go ahead and
管理员，我们将继续前进，
build one from a spring of vanilla
从香草的春天建造一个
spring good applications I'm gonna call
我会打电话给春季的好应用程序
this the micro-services dashboard
这是微服务仪表板
we'll use web support Eureka discovery
我们将使用网络支持Eureka发现
support actuator support and we'll hit
支持执行器支持，我们将
generate open this up and do allow the
产生开放，并允许
same sort of stuff as we did before
和以前一样
right so we'll say application of
对，所以我们说应用
properties spring that application that
属性推动了那个应用程序
name equals micro-services dashboard
名称等于微服务仪表板
server dot port equals eighty eighty
服务器点端口等于80
three and we'll register with you iike
三，我们将向您注册iike
as we have everything else will then
因为我们拥有其他一切
need to activate Dena Jay works Mike
需要激活Dena Jay的Mike
services to that dashboard dependencies
该仪表板依赖项的服务
so let's go ahead and add that to our
所以我们继续将其添加到我们的
build we'll go to Palm that XML and add
构建，我们将转到Palm的XML并添加
this here and I think the latest version
这在这里，我认为是最新版本
is 1.01 so 101 wait for that and we say
是1.01，所以101等待
at enable micro services dashboard
在启用微服务仪表板
server and that I think should do it so
服务器，我认为应该这样做
let's spin this up as well okay
让我们把它旋转起来好吗
localhost 8080 three there's our
本地主机8080三是我们的
dashboard and there we go we can see now
仪表板，现在我们可以看到
that it has discovered the nodes via the
它已经通过
registry and it is columned you know
注册表，并列您知道
sort of sorted them and put them into
对它们进行排序并放入
buckets back-end component these are
桶后端组件是
components that our Millah where if you
我们的Millah如果您在哪里
while they talk to other services so if
当他们与其他服务交谈时，如果
you had Redis for example if you had a
例如，如果您有一个Redis，
message in my sequel driver or something
续集驱动程序中的消息或其他内容
like this those kinds of beans would
这样的豆子会
automatically be reflected here in the
自动反映在这里
backend we'd see the micro services
后端，我们将看到微服务
themselves these are the Springwood
自己就是Springwood
applications they've been registered in
他们已经注册的应用程序
the registry and we have we have UI
注册表，我们有UI
components and resources which are api's
api的组件和资源
all reflected here and we can also see
全部都反映在这里，我们也可以看到
how they
他们怎么
to each other so if I click on for
彼此，所以如果我点击
example the Eureka registry I can see
我可以看到的尤里卡注册表示例
that it uses those two different bits of
它使用了这两个不同的位
middleware the the the forward slash API
中间件正斜杠API
which is exposed in our client B and
暴露在我们的客户B中
also in our client a is in turn gonna
同样在我们的客户中
talk to something in the backend here
在这里与后端交谈
right I mean in theory so we can see the
对，我的意思是理论上，所以我们可以看到
relationships that's very very
关系非常非常
convenient it shows just it shows us the
它显示的便利性只是向我们展示了
the distinct end points which services
服务的独特终点
have them if they are shared that you
有他们，如果他们分享你
can see that at a glance it shows you
一眼就能看出来
the states whether they're up or down or
指出他们是向上还是向下
whatever right so these are these are
随便吧，这些是
actuator and points as well this is from
执行器和要点也来自
the health endpoint and of course you
健康终点，当然你
can manually add these things as well
可以手动添加这些东西
but for our purposes it it is a very
但就我们的目的而言，这是一个非常
nice to just have them all sort of
很高兴让他们各种各样
automatically reflected right so we have
自动反映正确，所以我们有
looked at two different ways to to
研究了两种不同的方法
visualize your system and these are not
可视化您的系统，而这些不是
the the only ways to do this of course
当然，唯一的方法
but there's a lot of really a lot of
但实际上有很多
really nice opportunities here I would
我会在这里真的很好的机会
love to see the Micra services dashboard
喜欢看Micra服务仪表板
work sort of merged with the spring blab
工作种类与spring blab合并
and I'd love to have this visualization
我很想拥有这种可视化
but have the same at a glance
但一目了然
visualization of the actuator endpoints
致动器端点的可视化
and so on as the spring but I admit now
像春天一样，但我现在承认
that Ted you do get some of that here so
泰德，你确实在这里得到了一些
if I click on this I can see for example
如果我点击这个，我可以看到例如
the status and I can see basic
状态，我可以看到基本的
information here right that's I think
我认为这里的信息是正确的
that's convenient but it would be I used
那很方便，但是我会用
to have a little bit more right all
多一点吧
right so that was a quick look at some
对，所以快速浏览一下
of the dashboards that can help us get a
可以帮助我们获得
better understanding of our system
更好地了解我们的系统
through the spring cloud discovery
通过春季云发现
client abstraction and healthy living so
客户抽象和健康生活
thank you so much for your time and
非常感谢您的宝贵时间，
we'll see you around
我们会在附近见你